Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
- International Guards Union of America, Publication (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Daystrom Union favors strike if cut made, 1953-1954 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Extortion plot laid to two union aides, 1953-1954 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Union bids Police join it, 1953-1954 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Guards, 1953; Publication (Box 207, Folder 11)
    Author: International Guards Union of America
    Notes: vol.2:no.5-7
  - Item 6: Guards' Union files charge against GE, 1953-1954 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Museum Union waiting, 1953-1954 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Souvenir Program Second General Convention, 1953; Publication (Box 207, Folder 11)
- Cloth Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers' International Union, Publication (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1926; Publication (Box 208, Folder 1)
    Author: United Cloth Hat and Cap Makers of North America
  - Item 2: Press release, Publication (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Report: To the Officers and Delegates of the fifteenth biennial convention of the., Publication (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The Headgear Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 208, Folder 1)
    Author: Cloth Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers' International Union
    Notes: vol.11:no.6 (1926)
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workes International Union, Publication (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Declaration and resolution on Committee for Industrial Organization., 1936; Publication (Box 208, Folder 2)
    Author: United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workes International Union
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, Publication (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Jasper Q. Snark Hated Unions, Publication (Box 208, Folder 3)
    Notes: comic book
  - Item 2: Statement by Marx Lewis, General Secretary-Treasurer., Publication (Box 208, Folder 3)
    Author: Marx Lewis
- Edward W. Hamilton, Publication (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Hamilton plan for the settlement of labor disputes, 1938; Publication (Box 208, Folder 4)
    Author: Edward W. Hamilton
- International Guards Union of America, Publication (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-laws, Publication (Box 208, Folder 5)
    Author: General Aniline Guards, Local 101
    Notes: 2 pages
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1953; Publication (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Fifteenth Anniv. Dinner-Dance program, 1953; Publication (Box 208, Folder 5)
    Author: Pocketbook Workers Union, Local 29 (Newburgh, NY)
  - Item 4: Special convention Issue, June 1949, Publication (Box 208, Folder 5)
    Author: International Handbag, Luggage, Belt and Novelty Workers Union
- United Hatters, Cap, and Millinery Workers International Union, Publication (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: International Executive Board report to the second convention of the United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, 1936; Publication (Box 209, Folder 1)
    Author: United Hatters, Cap, and Millinery Workers International Union
  - Item 2: The Norwalk hat case, 1953-1954, Publication (Box 209, Folder 1)
- United Hatters, Cap & Millinery Workers International Union, Publication (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Sure it's a trick, Publication (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Who are we?, Publication (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: You don't have to be a magician, Publication (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Hat Pix, Publication (Box 209, Folder 2)
    Author: United Hatters, Cap & Millinery Workers International Union
  - Item 5: Hold it, Bud!, Publication (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: It's elementary!, Publication (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The sky?, 1953; Publication (Box 209, Folder 2)
    Author: Bendix Aviation
  - Item 8: Creative labor, Publication (Box 209, Folder 2)
- United Hatters, Cap & Millinery Workers International Union, Publication (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 100 Years, Local 11, 1951; Publication (Box 209, Folder 3)
    Notes: Souvenir booklet. 2 copies
  - Item 2: A brief outline of the United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, 1941; Publication (Box 209, Folder 3)
    Author: Max Zaritsky
  - Item 3: Our hat's in the ring...: and here's the story to tell about it, Publication (Box 209, Folder 3)
- United Hatters, Cap & Millinery Workers International Union, Publication (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Sure it's a trick but how is it done?, Publication (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The SURVEY, 1915; Publication (Box 209, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.33:no.16
- United Hebrew Trades, Publication (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Journal, 45th Anniversary, 1933; Publication (Box 209, Folder 5)
    Author: United Hebrew Trades
- Education unlimited, Publication (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Education unlimited: a handbook on union education in the South, 1945; Publication (Box 209, Folder 6)
    Author: Mary Lawrance
  - Item 2: How come me to be here?, 1949; Publication (Box 209, Folder 6)
    Author: Joanna Creighton Willimetz
    Notes: reprinted from the Wellesley Alumnae Magazine
  - Item 3: The Primer, Publication (Box 209, Folder 6)
    Notes: no. 1
- Wreckers, Publication (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Views differ on picketing, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Wildcat Strike ends at Oak Ridge Plant, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Wreckers walk out, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: More strikers to go back to atom plant, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Safety work is pushed in drain strike truce, 1950-1954 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Strike by wreckers hits 6 city projects, 1950-1954 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Union agent pleads guilty, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: 10-Cent pay raise granted laborers, 1950-1954 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: 7,000 HOD carriers will go on vacation, 1950-1954 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Can't embarrass Truman, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Laborers cancel wrecking strike, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Laborers seeking pay in above fraud, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Penalized in union theft, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Stoppage of work at 7 projects ends, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Strike by laborers halts building in Alton, wood river, 1950-1954 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Strike halts S. Oakland drain work, 1950-1954 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Strike threatens construction jobs, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Tube job stopped by labor dispute, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Union sues leader serving in house, 1949-1952 (Box 210, Folder 1)
- International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, Publication (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Arbitration award with M.A. Bongiovanni, Inc., 1956; Publication (Box 210, Folder 2)
    Author: International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America
- International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, Publication (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bay Area Conference of Hod Carriers., 1951; Publication (Box 210, Folder 3)
    Author: San Francisco Hod Carriers and Master Plasterers'
  - Item 2: Group insurance fund, 1953; Publication (Box 210, Folder 3)
    Author: Hod Carriers and Master Masons
  - Item 3: Group insurance plan, 1958; Publication (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Laborers welfare fund of Local 186, 1958; Publication (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Welfare and pension funds ... an educational series, 1961; Publication (Box 210, Folder 3)
- International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, Publication (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Civil actions - Shirley-Herman Company, Inc. vs. International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, 1948; Publication (Box 210, Folder 4)
- Thomas R. Roberts, Publication (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor through the years, 1950; Publication (Box 210, Folder 5)
    Author: Thomas R. Roberts
- Mason Tenders District Council, Publication (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The group insurance plan, 1948; Publication (Box 210, Folder 6)
    Author: Mason Tenders District Council
  - Item 2: Welfare fund, 1962; Publication (Box 210, Folder 6)
    Author: Laborers' Local 157
- International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, Publication (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Sandhogs, stiffs and rock men, 1964; Publication (Box 210, Folder 7)
    Author: International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America. Local 147
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers., Publication (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The new relations between capital and labor, 1929; Publication (Box 211, Folder 1)
    Author: Gustave Geiges
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers., Publication (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Death Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 211, Folder 2)
    Author: American Federation of Hosiery Workers
  - Item 2: Group Health and Accident Insurance Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Group Health and Accident Insurance Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Hosiery Industry Employees Pension Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 211, Folder 2)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers., Publication (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Dissenting opinion filed on October 9, 1931, Publication (Box 211, Folder 3)
    Author: George Wendell Maxey
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers., Publication (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A handbook for branch education committees, 1938; Publication (Box 211, Folder 4)
    Author: Lawrence Rogin
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers., Publication (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Accident and health protection for hosiery workers, 1947; Publication (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Employees' group health and accident insurance plan, Publication (Box 211, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers., Publication (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A Taft-Hartley case study: what has happened to the American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1958; Publication (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Making history in hosiery: the story of the American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1938; Publication (Box 211, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers., Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: How this union helps you, a message to seamless hosiery workers, Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Labor College of Philadelphia, is work such as this worth while?, Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The Why of the Kraemer Hosiery Dispute, Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: What can I do to help?, Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Another fighting chapter of the Allen-A lock-out, 1928; Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Court furthers illegal purpose when aiding union busting company, Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Earnings of full-fashioned hosiery workers in union mills, 1943; Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Girl leaders in hosiery workers' union, 1928; Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Join the union and be constitutional!, Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Pointers for organizers, prepared for the use of the American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Special communication to all members of the American Federation of Full Fashioned Hosiery Workers now engaged in the so-called insurgent strike against the National Agreement, 1928; Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: The American Federation of Full Fashioned Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: The fraud of company unionism, 1933; Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
    Author: American Federation of Hosiery Workers.
  - Item 14: The Hosiery Workers' Union, 1937; Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: The Why of the Allen-A lockout, 1928; Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Your right to organize is now law!, Publication (Box 211, Folder 7)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers., Publication (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Address of William f. Schnitzler to the 47th Convention of the American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1963; Publication (Box 211, Folder 8)
    Author: William F. Schnitzler
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers., Publication (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Application of branch to participate in hosiery workers staff pension plan, 1949; Publication (Box 211, Folder 9)
    Notes: Memo
  - Item 2: Authorization for withholding of contributions and payment to trustees of the hosiery workers, 1949; Publication (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Questions and Answers, Hosiery Workers Staff Pension Plan, 1949; Publication (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Staff pension plan, 1949; Publication (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Synopsis of staff pension plan, 1949; Publication (Box 211, Folder 9)
- American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Publication (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Wear union made hosiery and beat the 'yellow dog', 1922; Publication (Box 211, Folder 10)
- Hotel and Motel Trades Council, NY, Publication (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: 25th Anniversary of the First Union Contract, 1964; Publication (Box 211, Folder 11)
    Author: Hotel and Motel Trades Council, NY
  - Item 2: First New Union Show since "Pins & Needles", 1964; Publication (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Historic Day Family Medical care opening, 1962; Publication (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Hotel workers will appear in Union Anniv. Show, 1964; Publication (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: meeting minutes - Draft of Civil Rights Agreement, 1964; Publication (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: What you can get, who is covered in family plan, 1962; Publication (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Zero Mostel to appear as guest star in 'Twenty five candles' at Madison Square Garden, 1964; Publication (Box 211, Folder 11)
- Hotel and Motel Trades Council, NY, Publication (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bartenders and Culinary Workers Union, Local No. 126 - Group Insurance Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 212, Folder 1)
    Author: Hotel and Motel Trades Council
  - Item 2: Health and Welfare Plan of the Chicago (Downtown) Hotels and Local Joint Exec. Bd., 1950; Publication (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Pension Plan - Bartenders Union of New York City, Local 15, 1960; Publication (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: San Francisco Club Institute and San Francisco Local Joint Executive Bd. Group Life Ins. Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: San Francisco Restaurant and Tavern Welfare Fund Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Trust agreement (made in the city and county of San Francisco, State of California), 1950; Publication (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Welfare Plan - Bartenders Union of New York City, Local 15, 1960; Publication (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Your insurance plan, New York Hotel Trades Council and Hotel Association of New York City Insurance Fund, 1958; Publication (Box 212, Folder 1)
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report, Health & Welfare Trust (1st), 1951; Publication (Box 212, Folder 2)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees & Bartenders International Union
  - Item 2: Report, Health & Welfare Trust (3rd), 1953; Publication (Box 212, Folder 2)
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 50 years of progress: a brief history of our union, 1941; Publication (Box 212, Folder 3)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees, International Alliance Bartenders International League of America
  - Item 2: A brief history of our union, 1941; Publication (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Hotel and Restaurant Workers' International Union, 1940; Publication (Box 212, Folder 3)
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Our Insurance Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 212, Folder 4)
    Author: Hotel and Restaurant Workers Union, Local 16
- Childs Company, Publication (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1945; Publication (Box 212, Folder 5)
    Author: Childs Company
- Local 89, Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cooks & Assistants Union, Publication (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Your group insurance plan, 1947; Publication (Box 212, Folder 6)
    Author: Local 89, Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cooks & Assistants Union
  - Item 2: 2nd Annual Report, 1947; Publication (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Nicky gets his bicycle, 1948; Publication (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Nobody but nobody likes a chiseler, Publication (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: So why should you?, Publication (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: This is why we are on strike, Publication (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: You, too, can win union wages and union conditions, Publication (Box 212, Folder 6)
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Your union, what it is, how it operates, 1950; Publication (Box 212, Folder 7)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local no. 207 (Portland, Oregon)
- Cooks, Countermen, Soda Dispensers, Food Checkers, Cashiers and Assistants Union, Publication (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Amended, agreement and declaration of trust, 1952; Publication (Box 212, Folder 8)
    Author: Cooks, Countermen, Soda Dispensers, Food Checkers, Cashiers and Assistants Union
  - Item 2: By-law amendments, Publication (Box 212, Folder 8)
    Author: Local 325
  - Item 3: Local 325-By-Laws, 1941; Publication (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Pension Plan - Local 325, 1952; Publication (Box 212, Folder 8)
- Ithaca Bartenders' Union, Local 691, Publication (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Union news, 1950; Publication (Box 212, Folder 9)
    Author: Ithaca Bartenders' Union, Local 691
    Notes: vol.2-3. 2 copies
  - Item 2: We build a strong union, for security - happy workers - good working conditions., 1950; Publication (Box 212, Folder 9)
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Hotel and club voice, 1957; Publication (Box 213, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1957 October
  - Item 2: Hotel and club voice, 1958; Publication (Box 213, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1958 January
  - Item 3: Know your rights: under the Workmen's Compensation Law, Publication (Box 213, Folder 1)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local 6 (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 4: Local 6, 10th Anniversary - Feb. 4, 1938-Feb.4, 1948 - VOICE, Publication (Box 213, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.8:no.33
  - Item 5: This is your union, Publication (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Welfare fund, Publication (Box 213, Folder 1)
    Author: Dining Room Employees Union. Local 1
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: correspondence in Spanish, Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Five thousand cafeteria workers obtain five day, forty hour week., 1946; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
    Author: Cafeteria Employees Union, Local 302
  - Item 3: Good, Democratic trade unionism pays off!, Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local 15
  - Item 4: Inside Hotel Local 6, 1950; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
    Author: George Morris
  - Item 5: Presidential Elections - Oath of Office., 1952; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Questionnaire on mixed drinks, Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Security within your unionthe Bartenders Union Welfare fund, 1952; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
    Author: Bartenders Union of New York
  - Item 8: Special Report of the merger council - vol. 1, no. 1, 1954; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Striking Miami Beach Hotel Local, Opens Washington Publicity Office, 1955; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local 255
  - Item 10: To the men behind the stick from the men behind the stick, Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Wage earners group accident and health protection certificate no. 12,341, 1948; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
    Author: Union Casualty Company
  - Item 12: Welcome to Local 6, Meet your union, Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Administration of Cafeteria Employees Union, Local 302 re-elected., 1947; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Administration of Cafeteria Employees Union, Local 302,. Is re-elected by a majority of three to one, 1946; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Cafeteria Employees Union. Local 302 (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 15: Audit report - May 1st, 1946 to Dec. 31st, 1946, Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local 471
  - Item 16: By-laws, 1951; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Conozca al delegado de la union donde usted trabaja, Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Correspondence, 1948; Publication (Box 213, Folder 2)
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: conference folders, 1957; Publication (Box 213, Folder 3)
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: correspondence, Publication (Box 213, Folder 4)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local 1 (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 2: correspondence, 1962; Publication (Box 213, Folder 4)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local 60
  - Item 3: Financial report, 1962; Publication (Box 213, Folder 4)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local 325
  - Item 4: Industrial bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 213, Folder 4)
    Notes: (May, 1966)
  - Item 5: Local 1 Welfare Fund, 1963; Publication (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: memo, 1911; Publication (Box 213, Folder 4)
    Author: Chicago Cooks and Pastry Cooks Union. Local 865
  - Item 7: Rules governing hours and other working conditions of members, 1937; Publication (Box 213, Folder 4)
    Author: Cooks', Pastry Cooks' and Assistants' Union. Local No. 44
  - Item 8: Statement on 'Mystery' leaflet, Publication (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Wage scale and working conditions, 1942-1946 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    Notes: Booklets
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Culinarian, 1976; Publication (Box 213, Folder 5)
    Author: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local 22
    Notes: vol.1:no.5-7
  - Item 2: New York Culinarian, 1978; Publication (Box 213, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1
  - Item 3: Patronize these Union Restaurants in Midtown New York, Publication (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Patronize these Union Restaurants in Midtown New York; Welcome Convention Delegates, Publication (Box 213, Folder 5)
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Meeting minutes and copy of a Resolution, 1959; Publication (Box 213, Folder 6)
    Author: New York State Council of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union
  - Item 2: Report of President and Secretary-Treasurer. (43rd annual), 1957; Publication (Box 213, Folder 6)